http://www.theclarionnews.com/site/privacy.html

For the Record
F.Y.I.
For the Record
F.Y.I.
Site
This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for TheClarionNews.com. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Please read this policy closely. If you do not agree with the practices as described below, please do not use TheClarionNews.com.USE AND SHARING OF COLLECTED INFORMATIONYou must purchase an online subscription to view most of the content on TheClarionNews.com. Our subscription form requires that you provide your email address, contact information, and financial information. We use your contact information to contact you if we have trouble processing your subscription order, as well as to respond to you in the event that you contact us and do not provide adequate callback information. We use your financial information solely for the purpose of processing your order.We use your email address to contact you if we have trouble processing your subscription order or otherwise need to get in touch with you. We also use it to inform you when it is time to renew. Unless you ask us not to, we will also periodically contact you via email about specials, new products, changes to the website, or changes to the policies on our website.We are the lone owners of the information collected on TheClarionNews.com and will not sell or rent it in any way.We partner with a third party vendor to provide email notifications regarding updates on the website. These notifications are provided free of charge. Signup is optional and must be completed by the individual wishing to receive the email updates.ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER COLLECTED INFORMATIONAn online subscription must be purchased, and therefore personal information given, in order to access most of the content on TheClarionNews.com. We take the necessary precautions to protect your personal information both online and offline (see the “SECURITY” section below). If, however, you are still uncomfortable giving your personal information, you may continue to view the free access areas of TheClarionNews.com anonymously.An online subscription may be purchased online or offline. You may:Visit our Clarion office (located at located at 860 S. Fifth Avenue, Suite 4, Clarion, PA) or Oil City office (located at 1510 W. First Street, Oil City, PA) to pay in person.Call 814-677-8348 or 800-352-1002 and start your subscription over the phone using Visa, MasterCard or Discover.Complete the secure order form on our website.Complete a printable order form and send it with a check (made payable to Western PA Newspaper Company) or cash to: Clarion News, Attn: Online Subscription, 860 S. Fifth Ave., Suite 4, Clarion, PA 16214You can do the following at any time by contacting the Online Subscription Department using the phone number or email address provided on TheClarionNews.com:Learn what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Should you sign-up for the optional email notifications about updates on the site, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe option included at the bottom of each email.SECURITYWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Sensitive information collected on our website is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or by looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. Your credit card data is processed immediately and securely on our website; we do not receive it for manual processing.Offline, only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, payment recording or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is kept in a secure environment.COOKIESWe use "cookies" on TheClarionNews.com. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For example, we use a cookie to identify you so that you should only have to login once per viewing session instead of multiple times. The login feature on our site actually requires that cookies be enabled so that it can function properly. Please note that usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.Some of our business partners (for example, advertisers) may also use cookies on our site for their own purposes. They may be interested in collecting information such as specific information regarding your device (such as brand, internet browser, or operating system), the length of your viewing session, or your location. We, however, have no access to or control over these cookies.THIRD PARTY ADVERTISINGWe may use third party advertising companies in addition to our in-house advertising to serve you advertisements when you visit TheClarionNews.com. Advertisers and third parties may use web cookies and other tracking technologies to assist in showing you advertisements on our website about products and services that would be of interest to you. For example, they may collect and use information about your visits to our website and other websites so that they can serve you an advertisement about a special offer from a business you frequent. The tracking data does not identify you personally. The goal of this process is to create a more enjoyable viewing experience for you. You can learn more about online advertising on the Network Advertising Initiative’s website by visiting https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/.You can choose not to receive targeted advertising. The Network Advertising Initiative and Digital Advertising Alliance both have free opt-out tools available. You can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s website at http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/ or the Digital Advertising Alliance’s website at http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/.THIRD PARTY LINKSTheClarionNews.com contains links to other sites. Some of these links are to company-affiliated sites such as TheDerrick.com, while others are to outside sites such as advertisers’ sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. Nonetheless, we care about the integrity of our site and welcome you to submit any feedback about these sites.TERMS OF SERVICEPlease visit the Terms of Use section on our website to read the complete Terms of Use.UPDATESOur Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time and all updates will appear on this page. The date of the most recent revisions will appear at the bottom of this page, so please be sure to check back periodically. Your continued use of the site following any modifications to this Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy.If you feel that we are not abiding by the practices described in our Privacy Policy, or you have any questions about our policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 814-677-8348 or via email at circulation.theclarionnews@gmail.com.Date of last revision: March 26, 2018
Click to subscribe to TheClarionNews.com!
Click to subscribe to TheClarionNews.com!Click to subscribe to TheClarionNews.com!
Latest e-Edition
The Clarion News
To view our latest e-Edition click the image on the left.
Most Popular
Articles
Articles'Bathroom pod' builder bringing 50-130 jobs to KnoxClarion zip code posts highest infection totalEvents tightening ammunition suppliesClarion Hospital moves COVID testing siteComputing school infection rates is tricky businessClarion Hospital sees increase in virus patientsLavan and Brown named Sportsmanship I Sportsperson of the YearDistrict Court 18-3-01 120820ACV brings struggling students back to buildingClarion Area board remains split on procedures
Photos + Videos
Scenes from the 2019 ALF car and motorcycle shows
Facebook
Twitter
WhatsApp
SMS
Email
Newsletters
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
News Updates
Want to receive breaking news alerts, a preview of headlines for new editions, and other news updates? Sign up today!
Promotional Offers
Looking for a good deal?  Sign up to receive promotional offers from us!
Manage your lists
© Copyright 2020 The Clarion News, 860 S. Fifth Avenue, Suite 4 Clarion, PA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
